[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous Japanese cherry trees were planted in Washington, D.C., around the Tidal Basin at the request of which US First Lady?", "correct_answer": "Helen Taft", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty Ford", "Anna Eleanor Roosevelt", "Lou Henry Hoover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is seen in the dumbwaiter in one of the funniest scenes from the 1986 comedy movie The Money Pit, produced by Steven Spielberg?", "correct_answer": "Raccoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Rat", "Koala", "Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steven Christopher Parker, who plays a student in Juno, is probably more famous to TV viewers as Harold Zelinsky in this show.", "correct_answer": "ER", "incorrect_answers": ["The Guiding Light", "Monk", "Third Rock from the Sun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who hired the vigilantes to kill Leroy in The last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "Eddie Arkadian", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocko", "The Shogun", "Beast"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in 1978, 1990 or 2002, what would your lunar sign be?", "correct_answer": "horse", "incorrect_answers": ["snake", "sheep", "rat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the apparent path of the sun around the sky called?", "correct_answer": "Ecliptic", "incorrect_answers": ["Revolution", "Zodiac", "Corona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many continents are generally considered to be there on Earth?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "6", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the physical disability of Virginia Cherrills character in the 1931 movie City Lights?", "correct_answer": "She cant see.", "incorrect_answers": ["She cant walk.", "She cant talk.", "She cant hear."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Lewis have to keep a hat on at all times in the movie Meet the Robinsons?", "correct_answer": "So the Robinsons wouldnt see his hair", "incorrect_answers": ["It was the only thing he had from his mother", "Thats just the way the character was created", "He had head lice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nicknames has been given to the U.S. state of Illinois?", "correct_answer": "Corn State", "incorrect_answers": ["Rubber State", "Cotton State", "Paper State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which super computer lost a match to Garry Kasparov?", "correct_answer": "Deep Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Cycletrone-Check", "Cray-1", "Super Check"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would speak English as their first language?", "correct_answer": "59", "incorrect_answers": ["352", "154", "659"]}]